// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the purpose of CSS Flexbox? ",
    answer: "To create flexible layouts with a single-dimensional structure ",
    options: [
      "To create responsive images ",
      "To create responsive tables",
      "To create flexible layouts with a single-dimensional structure ",
      "To create animations"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which CSS property is used to control the capitalization of text? ",
    answer: "text-transform",
    options: [
      "text-transform",
      "text-case",
      "text-uppercase",
      "font-case "
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which CSS property is used to set the style of underlined text",
    answer: "text-decoration",
    options: [
      "text-decoration",
      "text-style ",
      "text-underline ",
      "text-variant"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What does the box-sizing property control in CSS? ",
    answer: "The size of the border box",
    options: [
      "The size of the border box",
      "The size of the content box",
      "The size of the margin box",
      "The size of the entire element box"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "what is the most significant heading in Html?",
    answer: "H1",
    options: [
      "H1",
      "H2",
      "H3",
      "H4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is JavaScript primarily used for?",
    answer: "Adding interactivity to websites",
    options: [
      "Styling web pages",
      "Building databases",
      "Adding interactivity to websites",
      "Creating 3D animations"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which keyword is used to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
    answer: "let",
    options: [
      "var",
      "int",
      "string",
      "let"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a valid data type in JavaScript?",
    answer: "float",
    options: [
      "string",
      "boolean",
      "number",
      "float"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'if' statement in JavaScript?",
    answer: "To make decisions based on conditions",
    options: [
      "To create a loop",
      "To define a function",
      "To make decisions based on conditions",
      "To declare variables"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "CSS stands for?",
    answer: "Cascading style sheet",
    options: [
      "Cascading style sheet",
      "cascading sheet style",
      "case size serve",
      "column size style"
    ]
  }
    
];